electronshops.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy

Electronshops respects your privacy. From our business, around the world, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to offer help and keep a good relationship with you, for example, to process your order, provide service and support, and send you new release products or any update news, we will never sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the electronshops family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect electronshops, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help electronshops fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share electronshops's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact electronshops with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.

### Privacy and data security

At electronshops, your right to privacy and data security is a very important. That's why, when you visit electronshops.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the internet.

###  

### Electronshops only uses your personal information for specific purposes

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with electronshops. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on electronshops.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from electronshops. Agents or contractors of electronshops who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for electronshops. Electronshops may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. In addition, electronshops may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if electronshops reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect electronshops, its customers, or the public.

### Electronshops will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of electronshops for the purpose of performing services for electronshops.

### Electronshops wants to help you keep your personal information accurate

To view or edit the information that has been stored online, please visit the my account of the electronshops web site.

### Internet commerce

The online store at electronshops.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. Electronshops is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called ssl encryption, at our payment gateways. It has always been a electronshops practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.

### Customized experience

We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At electronshops, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.electronshops.com. Electronshops has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the electronshops.com site.
